Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11 Locals, 2.
  - Local 166F
    - Local 166F Sheboygan Situation, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Local 166F 710 Forms, 1950-1962 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Local 167F
    - Local 167F Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Erwin Hoehnke Regarding Organization, May 21, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Local 167F Outgoing Correspondence, Erwin Hoehnke Regarding Organization, May 18, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Local 167F Publications, Leaflet Regarding Negotiations, June 17, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Local 167F Arbitration Award, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Local 167F Chicago Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Local 167F Monies Held in Escrow by IUE, 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Local 167F 710 Forms, 1949-1967 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Local 169F
    - Local 169F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949-April 21, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Local 169F Outgoing Correspondence, John Volz to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations with June 14, 1950, Company Offer; June 14, 1950, Union Counter-Proposal; and Original Union Demands, June 19, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Local 173F
    - Local 173F La Porte, IN, Correspondence, 1956-1968 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 179F
    - Local 179F 710 Forms, 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 182F
    - Local 182F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949-March 30, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Local 182F Incoming Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Julius Emspak to William Cusuck Regarding Dues and Membership Drive, April 23, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Eugene Bonk Regarding Strikes, October 7, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, October 17, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, October 24, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, October 31, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, November 7, 1952; 6.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, November 14, 1952; 7.
      - Emspak to Bonk Regarding Strikes, November 21, 1952; 8.
      - Emspak to George Walton Regarding Per Capita, April 13, 1955; 9.
    - Local 182F Outgoing Correspondence, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - William Cusack to Julius Emspak Regarding Membership Drive and Dues, April 13, 1951; 1.
      - Cusack to Emspak Regarding Membership Drive and Dues, August 9, 1951; 2.
    - Local 182F Per Capita Reports, October 1949-March 1955 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Local 182F Strike Expenses, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Local 182F Mailing List, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Samuel Hamburger to Julius Emspak, February 28, 1955; 1.
      - Emspak to Hamburger, March 2, 1955; 2.
    - Local 182F Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Membership Drive and Dues, August 23, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 183F
    - Local 183F Officers Lists, November 1-25, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Local 183F Incoming Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Julius Emspak to James Rusmussen Regarding National Strike Fund, November 3, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Rusmussen Regarding Plant Closing, April 29, 1955; 2.
    - Local 183F Outgoing Correspondence, James Rasmussen to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 23, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Local 183F Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Irvin Weir Regarding Plant Closure, April 29, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 186F
    - Local 186F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949-December 15, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Local 186F Incoming Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Ernest DeMaio to Leo Coleman Regarding Finances, January 29, 1952; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Oscar Zimmer Regarding Per Capita, December 30, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Coleman Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Wages, January 16, 1952; 3.
    - Local 186F Outgoing Correspondence, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Charles Van Der Missen to Julius Emspak Regarding Union Shop, Negotiations, and Inter-union Rivalry, January 12, 1952; 1.
      - Van Der Missen to Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry and Negotiations, March 13, 1952; 2.
    - Local 186F Publications, "The Attitude" Leaflet Regarding Negotiations, American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, and Work to Rule, December 9, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Local 186F American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - James DeWitt to Julius Emspak, August 13, 1954; 1.
      - Emspak to DeWitt, August 19, 1954; 2.
    - Local 186F National Labor Relations Board Decision Regarding Union Shop, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 187F
    - Local 187F Chicago Correspondence, 1956-1966 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Local 187F Chicago National Lead Correspondence, 1970-1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Local 189F
    - Local 189F Chicago Correspondence, 1950-1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Local 189F Brookfield, IL, International Molding Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Local 189F Legislative Committee and Political Action, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Local 190F
    - Local 190F Incoming Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Julius Emspak to Walter Sheuchuk Regarding Strikes, September 26, 1955; 1.
      - James Matles to Edward Ryan Regarding Grievances and Safety, June 2, 1952; 2.
    - Local 190F Outgoing Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - John Harth to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Strikes, and 1955 UE Convention, September 19, 1955; 1.
      - Edward Ryan to UE Regarding Grievances, Safety, and Factionalism with Grievances, May 26, 1952; 2.
    - Local 190F Chicago Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Local 190F Chicago Phoenix Closures, 1964-1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Local 190F Strikes, Subsidies, and Other Monies, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Local 190F Constitution Correspondence, 1956-1994 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Local 198F
    - Local 198F Strikes, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Local 198F Chicago Correspondence, 1958-1964 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Local 202AF
    - Local 202AF Officers Lists, November 1, 1949-February 14, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Local 202AF Incoming Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Julius Emspak to Anton Smolke Regarding Strikes, October 31, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to W. Sliwa Regarding Per Capita, April 13, 1955; 2.
    - Local 202AF Per Capita, February-March 1955 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Local 202AF Correspondence, Jack Burch to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, September 13, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Local 202F
    - Local 202F Officers Lists, May 19, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Local 202F Incoming Correspondence, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Julius Emspak to Anton Smolke Regarding Strikes, November 7, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Paul Barletta, November 14, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Barletta Regarding Strikes, November 21, 1952; 3.
    - Local 202F Outgoing Correspondence, Robert Moorman to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 11, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Local 202F Per Capita, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Local 202F Charter Reissue, 1951-1953 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Julius Emspak to Milt Burns, June 21, 1951; 1.
      - Emspak to Burns, July 20, 1951; 2.
      - Memo, November 12, 1952; 3.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Ernest DeMaio, November 18, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to DeMaio, January 12, 1953; 5.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Grant Oakes, March 23, 1953; 6.
      - Gwen Shadd to Ray Klausner, April 1, 1953; 7.
    - Local 202F Correspondence, Thelma Boldman to Janet Barish Regarding Strikes and Officers, November 10, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Local 204F
    - Local 204F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949-March 12, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Local 204F Outgoing Correspondence, Joseph Schwoerer to UE Regarding Disaffiliation, June 22, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Local 204F Leaflet, "I Would Like" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, July 7, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Local 204F District 50 Inter-union Rivalry, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - James DeWitt to Department of Labor, June 18, 1955; 1.
      - DeWitt to William Hayssen, June 20, 1955; 2.
      - James Matles Memo to Legal, June 20, 1955; 3.
      - Basil Pollitt to DeWitt, June 21, 1955; 4.
      - DeWitt to Julius Emspak, June 22, 1955; 5.
      - DeWitt Letter Excerpt, June 23, 1955; 6.
      - Emspak to DeWitt, July 1, 1955; 7.
  - Local 208F
    - Local 208F Outgoing Correspondence, Joseph Vitosky to UE Regarding Per Capita, September 2, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Local 208F Notes of Delinquency, May 1958 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Local 208F 710 Forms, 1950-1956 (Box 12, Folder 49)